<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Patch>

	<Operation Class="PatchOperationFindMod">
		<mods>
			<li>Magical Menagerie</li>
		</mods>
		<match Class="PatchOperationSequence">
			<operations>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Ahuizotl"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Ahuizotl is a legendary creature in Aztec myth. It is described as dog-like, its waterproof fur often clumping up to create spikes. The ahuizotl has hands capable of manipulation and an additional hand on its tail. The ahuizotl is feared due to its liking for human flesh, especially nails, eyes, and teeth. It is said to live in or near the water and to use the hand on the end of its tail to snatch its prey, dragging the person into the depths to drown them.\n\nSpecial abilities: Ahuizotl are adept at using the hand at the end of their tail to grab their prey and claw at them with their paws, making a retreat quite difficult if engaged in close quarters.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Basilisk"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>In European bestiaries, the basilisk is a legendary reptile, reputed to be a serpent king, who can cause death with a single glance. Pliny the Elder described the basilisk as a serpent with a white spot on the head, strongly resembling a diadem. It was said to have an extremely noxious effect on plants and all kind of vegetation, destroying and rotting all plants surrounding it.\n\nSpecial Abilities: The basilisk is a particularly unpleasant beast. Its gaze attack can petrify its victims, and grass and bushes surrounding it will slowly rot and turn into withered husks, feeding the basilisk in the process. Luckily, basilisks aren't very common.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Catoblepas"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Catoblepas is a legendary creature from Ethiopia, said to have the body of a cape buffalo and an oversized head that is constantly pointing downwards due to its great weight.\n\nSpecial Abilities: The stare of the Catoblepas can turn people into stone. They are not naturally aggressive, but this dangerous ability makes sure they have no natural predators.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Cerberus"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>In Greek mythology, Cerberus, often referred to as the hound of Hades, is a three-headed dog that guards the gates of the Underworld to prevent the dead from leaving. Cerberus was the offspring of the monsters Echidna and Typhon, and is primarily known for his capture by Heracles, one of Heracles' twelve labours.\n\nSpecial abilities: Cerberi are harder to train than regular dogs, and they aren't as intelligent, but having three heads makes them very VERY dangerous combat animals, specially when modified with bionic jaw implants.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_CeryneianHind"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>In Greek mythology, the Ceryneian Hind was a mythical creature that lived in Ceryneia, Greece, and took the form of an enormous deer, larger than a bull, with golden antlers like a stag. To bring it back alive to Eurystheus in Mycenae was the third labour of Heracles.\n\nSpecial Abilities: The Ceryneian Hind (and by extension, Hart, since they were created in both genders) is a very fast creature, though it can't be trained as a mount as well as Unicorns or Pegasi. It produces milk.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Chimera"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The chimera was a monstrous fire-breathing hybrid creature of Lycia in Asia Minor, composed of the parts of a lion, with the head of a goat protruding from its back, and a tail that ends with a snake's head.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Chimeras are both slightly venomous and fire breathing, making them quite dangerous, and not only to their enemies! Chimeras just LOVE wooden colonies. Oh, they can also be milked...</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_ErymanthianBoar"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Erymanthian Boar was a gargantuan, monstruous wild hog that inhabited the slopes of mount Erymanthus, occasionally laying waste to the farmers' fields. The boar's capture was the objective of the Fourth Labour of Heracles. To capture the boar, Heracles drove it into thick snow, considerably slowing its progress and advantage.\n\nSpecial Abilities: The tusks of the Erymanthian Boar can cause some serious wounds that keep bleeding and causing further injuries, making them VERY dangerous in close quarters.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Fenghuang"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Fenghuang is a legendary bird in East Asian mythologies symbolizing high virtue and grace. The fenghuang also symbolizes the union of yin and yang, and it is believed that the bird only appears in areas or places that are blessed with utmost peace and prosperity or happiness. Traditionally described as a composite of many birds it is also often called a "Chinese Phoenix", although similarities with the western Phoenix are superficial.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Tamed Fenghuangs radiate an aura of peace and tranquility, elevating the spirits of those nearby.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Griffin"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Griffin is a creature with the body, tail, and back legs of a lion; the head and wings of an eagle; and an eagle's talons as its front feet. Griffins are especially powerful and majestic creatures, known for guarding treasure and priceless possessions, and valued as trusted steeds.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Griffins are excellent mounts, receiving bonuses to speed and armour when mounted (this needs the Giddy-up! Battle Mounts mod).</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Ieltxu"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Ieltxu is a genie bird in Basque mythology. Usually depicted as a fire breathing, pitch black raven, the Ieltxu is not a malicious creature, though it is often described as mischievous. Ieltxu are creatures of the night, usually appearing in dark forests under the cover of darkness.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Ieltxu can breathe fire when threatened. They are nocturnal creatures that sleep during the day.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Kappa"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The kappa is a river imp in Japanese folklore, depicted as green, human-like beings with webbed hands and feet and a turtle-like carapace on their backs. A depression on their head, their "dish", holds a tiny amount of water, and the kappa is severely weakened if this water spills or dries. Although kappa are often seen as mischievous, they are not inherently malicious. In fact, once befriended, kappa may perform any number of tasks for human beings, such as helping farmers irrigate their land.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Kappa are cowardly, fleeing combat if they lose too much health. Properly trained kappa ("Guard" skill at least) can help colonists on harvesting tasks.</description>	
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Kitsune"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Kitsune is a legendary creature from Japanese folklore, depicted as a quite intelligent fox-like being possessing paranormal abilities that increase with its age and wisdom. Kitsune have as many as nine tails. Generally, a greater number of tails indicates an older and more powerful Kitsune.\n\nSpecial Abilities: When tamed, Kitsune slowly regenerate the wounds of nearby colonists and animals.</description>	
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_LernaeanHydra"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Lernaean Hydra is a serpentine water monster in Greek and Roman mythology. Its lair was the lake of Lerna in the Argolid, hence its name. The hydra possesses virulently poisonous breath and blood, and impressive regenerative capabilities. Slaying the hydra was the objective of the Second Labour of Heracles.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Hydras can regenerate wounds quite fast. Hydras are dangerous in close combat, but their real danger comes from their poisonous acidic breath. Luckily, they are usually quite shy creatures and don't tend to approach humans.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_LesserWyvern"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>In Medieval European heraldry, the wyvern is a winged bipedal dragon, appearing in numerous standards and coats of arms. The wyvern in heraldry and folklore is rarely fire-breathing, unlike the four-legged dragon. Instead, wyverns are usually associated with poison, either in the form of venomous fangs or their dangerous barbed tail.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Lesser Wyverns are extremely venomous, resistant to damage, and almost indifferent to extreme pain. Luckily, they are very rare. Contrary to Greater Wyverns, they can't spit poison (to see Greater Wyverns, download our RimWorld - Witcher Monster Hunt mod!).</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Manticore"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Manticore is a monstrous legendary creature in Persian mythology. It has a hybrid leonine-humanoid head, the body of a lion and a scorpion tail of venomous spines similar to porcupine quills. This manticore has also been modified to have non-functional chiropteran wings, even though historical depictions of the creature didn't include them. The manticore is a fierce predator, capable of stalking its prey and attack from range.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Manticores can throw poisoned quills from their scorpion-like tails.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Pegasus"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Pegasus is a mythical winged divine horse, and one of the most recognized creatures in Greek mythology. Pegasi are white stallions with a pair of feathered wings sprouting from their back. Mythological pegasi were said to be able to fly using those wings, however these creatures seem to sport them just for aesthetic reasons, as there is no amount of genetic engineering that could make such flimsy wings to support their weight. They are appreciated as fast and dependable steeds.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Pegasi are excellent mounts, receiving a huge bonus to speed when mounted (this needs the Giddy-up! Battle Mounts mod).</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Phoenix"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>In ancient Egyptian and later Greek and Roman mythology, a phoenix is a long-lived bird that cyclically regenerates or is otherwise born again, usually in a massive conflagration that lays waste to anything else around it. Symbolically, the Phoenix has always been associated with concepts of rebirth, renewal and perseverance.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Attacks from a Phoenix can set their targets on fire. When the Phoenix dies, it will explode and create a fire resistant egg (or sometimes two). After a while, a new Phoenix will hatch from this egg.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Qilin"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Qilin is a mythical hooved chimerical creature known in Chinese and other East Asian cultures, said to appear with the imminent arrival or passing of a sage or illustrious ruler. Qilins' bodies are partially scaled and shaped like a deer, and they sport a pair of impressive antlers on their heads.\n\nThough Qilin are usually peaceful creatures, they have a nasty tendency to set their enemies on fire when provoked.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Salamander"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The salamander is an amphibian which, as with many real creatures, often has been ascribed fantastic and sometimes occult qualities not possessed by the real organism. The legendary salamander in Classical, Medieval, and Renaissance lore is often depicted as a typical salamander or a snake in shape with a lizard-like form, but is usually ascribed an affinity with elemental fire.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Salamanders radiate incredible amounts of heat, making them very dangerous (or very useful) in close spaces. Their eggs have that quality too, and they explode upon hatching. A salamander's bite can set their target on fire.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Tlilcoatl"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The tlilcoatl ("black snake" in nahuatl) is a predatory reptile in Mexican folklore. Tlilcoatls have glossy black scales, a bifurcated tail and grow to a considerable size. They can breathe a dangerous poisonous gas that quickly suffocates their victims.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Tlilcoatls are virulently venomous, with a dangerous bite and a very nasty breath attack. They will however only attacks humans defensively.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Unicorn"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The unicorn is a legendary creature that has been described since antiquity as a beast with a single large, pointed, spiraling horn projecting from its forehead. The unicorn was depicted in ancient seals of the Indus Valley Civilization and was mentioned by the ancient Greeks. The Unicorn was commonly described as an extremely wild woodland creature, a symbol of purity and grace. Its horn is said to have the power to render poisoned water potable and to heal sickness.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Unicorns are excellent mounts, receiving a huge bonus to speed when mounted (this needs the Giddy-up! Battle Mounts mod).</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_WildMinotaur"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>In Greek mythology, the Minotaur is a mythical creature portrayed in Classical times with the head and tail of a bull and the body of a man. He dwelt at the center of the Labyrinth, which was an elaborate maze-like construction designed by the architect Daedalus and his son Icarus, on the command of King Minos of Crete. The Minotaur was eventually killed by the Athenian hero Theseus. The mythological Minotaur was often portrayed as a cunning beast, whereas this creature possesses a very basic, instinctual intelligence.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Wild Minotaurs can pound the ground with their hooves, producing ground tremors.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_WillOWisp"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The Will-O'-Wisp is a creature from English folklore consisting of an atmospheric ghost light seen by travelers at night, especially over bogs, swamps or marshes. It is said to mislead travelers by resembling a flickering lamp or lantern.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Will-O'-Wisps can barely be considered living creatures, resembling really strange bacteria more than anything else. They reproduce by asexual fission, need almost no sustenance, and are immune to temperature extremes, toxic environments, fire and psychic attacks. If threatened, which isn't often, they can breathe a cloud of multicoloured particles that seems to be harmful to living creatures.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
				<li Class="PatchOperationReplace">
					<xpath>/Defs/ThingDef[defName = "MM_Xiezhi"]/description</xpath>
					<value>
						<description>The xiezhi is a legendary creature in Chinese mythology, as well as in Korean mythology where it is known as haetae. The xiezhi is usually represented as a cross between a lion and a goat, with a single horn on its forehead. Xiezhi are innately attuned to good and evil, being able to instinctively know the innocent from the guilty.\n\nSpecial Abilities: Xiezhi will viciously attack pirates, goring them with their justice-seeking horn.</description>
					</value>
				</li>
			</operations>
		</match>
	</Operation>
  
</Patch>